2nd Floor, 13 Baggot St Upper, Dublin 4, D04 W7K5

<u>W: www.sralocum.com</u> <u>E: info@sralocum.com</u> P: 01-6854700 & 01-6994321

Fax: 01-6852538



CURRICULUM VITAE

SRA Locum Template

It is of importance that all our CVs are received in the same format. We appreciate if you could fill this template out and return to <u>info@sralocum.com</u>. Should you have any questions please contact: Shahid Ali, Locum Coordination Consultant, SRA Locum (00353 1 685 4700).

MOHAMED SIDDIG SAIED ELSHAIKH MBBS, MRCPI

Perso	nal	De	tails
I CIBU	<i>iiui</i>	$\boldsymbol{\nu}$	uuuus

Surname: Elshaikh

First Names: Mohamed Siddig Saied

Address: 120 Premier square, Finglas Road, Dublin

11.Co Dublin.

E-mail: MOHAMEDSIDDIG80@GMAIL.COM

Phone: 0873493769 **Place**

& date of Birth: Sudan

Nationality: Irish, Sudanese

Driving license: Full

Sudan Medical Council Medical: Full Registration (21525)

Saudi commission for health

Council Ireland: 405483

Personal statement:

Over the past 15 years since graduation and internship, I have gained extensive, broad experience in all aspects of our specialty. I have successfully

2nd Floor, 13 Baggot St Upper, Dublin 4, D04 W7K5

W: www.sralocum.com

E: info@sralocum.com

P: 01-6854700 & 01-6994321

Fax: 01-6852538



complete RCPI Obstetrics. I have continued my (any mangment skills). In the year after finishing my rotation, the ultimate goal of working as a consultant in Ireland with the skills I obtain.

Education:

- MRCOG 1_{st} part &2nd Part,

2019

- MRCPI OBS&GYN,

2016

- Part 1 exam obsterics and gynecology Sudan medical specialization board, 2009
- MBBS, Faculty of medicine, University of Khartoum, 2005
- UCD diploma (early pregnancy ultrasound. Fetal growth,Fetal wellbeing)

2020-2021

Prizes and grants:

- First class honours(Prize) in Obstetrics & Gynaecology, Faculty Of
 Medicine University of Khartoum.
- Second class honours in Medicine, Paediatrics, Surgery, Community
 Medicine, Microbiology, Pathology, Anatomy, Biochemistry, Faculty of
 Medicine University of Khartoum.
 1999-

2nd Floor, 13 Baggot St Upper, Dublin 4, D04 W7K5

W: www.sralocum.com

E: info@sralocum.com

P: 01-6854700 & 01-6994321

Fax: 01-6852538



Locum History

Date	Grade	Area		
2 nd & 3 rd April 2022	Obs & Gynae Registrar	Midland Regional Hospital Portlaoise		
23 rd April 2022	Obs & Gynae Registrar	Midland Regional Hospital Portlaoise		
29th April - 1st May 2022	Obs & Gyane Registrar	Midland Regional Hospital Portlaoise		
13 th – 15 th May 2022	Obs & Gynae Registrar	Midland Regional Hospital Portlaoise		
21st May 2022	Obs & Gynae SHO	Midland Regional Hospital Portlaoise		

Employment history:

Current Employment:

- Senior Registrar(Acting Assistant master Jan2021-May2021), National maternity Hospital

July 2020-present

Supervisor: Prof.Shane Higgins

Previous Employments:

- Gynaecology Registrar, Connolly Hospital, July 2019-July 2020

Supervisor: Dr.Naomi Burke

-Registrar ,Rotunda Hospital Jan 2017-Jan2018

- Senior Registrar, Rotunda Hospital, Jan 2018-July 2019

Supervisor: Prof. Michael Geary

- Registrar, Mayo University Hospital, Jan 2015-Jan 2017

2nd Floor, 13 Baggot St Upper, Dublin 4, D04 W7K5

W: www.sralocum.com

E: info@sralocum.com

P: 01-6854700 & 01-6994321

Fax: 01-6852538



Supervisor: Dr.Meabh Nibhuinneain

- SHO Mayo University Hospital,

Jan 2014-Jan2015

Supervisor: Dr. Ulrich Bartels

- Medical officer(obstetrics & gynaecology, paediatrics, surgery and medicine)

Bareg PHC. Kingdom, Saudi Arabia

Oct 2009- Mar2013

- SHO Obstetrics & Gynaecology, Elginaina Teaching Hospital, Sudan

June2007-August2009

- Internship under supervision of Sudanese federal ministry of Health, Sudan, November 2005- May2007 at the following details:
- 1- **Pediatrics**, (Shendi Teaching hospital, Shendi), 3 months.
- 2- Orthopaedics (Khartoum North Teaching Hospital): 2 months.
- 3- Obstetrics and Gynecology (Khartoum Teaching Hospital): 3 months.
- 4- Urology (Omdurman Teaching Hospital): 3 months.
- 5- **Medicine** (Omdurman Teaching Hospital): 3 months.
- 6- General Surgery (Kassala teaching Hospital): 3 months.

Audit:

- -10 LW Audits Mayo university Hospital 2015/2016
- -Anaemia and Hb check in ANC Rotunda 2018
- -LGA National Maternity Hopsital 2022

Management:

2nd Floor, 13 Baggot St Upper, Dublin 4, D04 W7K5

W: www.sralocum.com

E: info@sralocum.com

P: 01-6854700 & 01-6994321

Fax: 01-6852538



- MOH committee member	National	Maternity	Hopsital	2021
------------------------	-----------------	------------------	----------	------

Teaching:			

- **Teaching** Junior registrar and BST SHO a range of skills surgical and management of Obstertric /Gynaecology cases **2019-Present.**

Research:

- The Realtionship Between Scar length and Experience of pain in women post cesearen section.

Publications:

- Case Report: Extended Use of Intrauterine Balloon Tamponade as Effective Management of Life Threatening Menorrhagia with Unknown Cause. Mohamed Abdelrahman, Shayi Dezayi, Feras J Alkharouf, M Elshaikh, Hassan Rajab and Connor Hariety, ECCMC- 21- CR-154.
- -CaseReport: Postpartum Haemorrhage in setting of an Undiagnosed Müllerian Anomaly. O'Riordan, Sarah L., **Elshaikh Mohamed**, O'Brien, Donal, Carroll, Stephen **FIGO Oct 2021.**
- Case Report : Peri-Clitoral Abscess Diagnosis with Management Options: and Literature Review.
- M. Elshaikh, Mohamed Abdelrahman, Feras J. Alkharouf, Rawia Ahmed, Hassan Rajab, MAR Gynecology 1.3 (2021).

Courses:		

2nd Floor, 13 Baggot St Upper,

Dublin 4, D04 W7K5

W: www.sralocum.com

E: info@sralocum.com

P: 01-6854700 & 01-6994321

Fax: 01-6852538



-ACLS Mayo university Hospital May 2015

-ACLS PMI online April 2020

- **BLS** Mayo University Hospital November 2018

- Neonatal Resuscitation course MUH April 2015

- **PROMT courses, Rotunda Hospital** November

2018/2019 - K2 MEDICAL SYSTEM CTG

2019/2021

References:

- **1.Prof.Shane** Higgins, shiggins@nmh.ie Master National maternity Hospital.
- **2.Dr.Steve Carroll , scarroll@nmh.ie** , Consultant obstetrics and gynaecology National Maternity Hopsital.
- **3. Dr.Naomi Burke** <u>nburke@rotunda.ie</u> Consultant obstetrics and gynaecology Connolly/Rotunda Hospital.
- **4. Dr.Khusal Chummun, <u>kchummun@rotunda.ie</u>**, Consultant obstetrics and gynaecology Connolly/Rotunda Hospital.
- 5- Prof. Michael Geary mgeary@rotunda.ie,
- 5- Dr. Shron Cooley <u>scooley@rotunda.ie</u>, obstetrics and gynaecology Rotunda Hospital.
- 6- Dr.Meabh Nibhuinneain, Consultant obstetrics and gynaecology MGH Castlebar, meabh.nibhuinneain@hse.ie
- 7- Dr.Ulrich Bartels,. Consultant obstetrics and gynaecolog ,MGH Castlebar, ulrich.bartels@hse.ie, .